<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SNLab - Systems Networking Lab</title>
    <link>/</link>
      <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>SNLab - Systems Networking Lab</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2019 21:21:50 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>SNLab - Systems Networking Lab</title>
      <link>/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tongji-Yale Open Access Proceedings 2016 - 2019 is Published</title>
      <link>/post/tongji-yale-pub-2019-release/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2019 21:21:50 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/tongji-yale-pub-2019-release/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The open access proceedings of Tongji-Yale Systems Networking Laboratory (SNLab) (2016 - 2019) is available now. Members from SNLab have published 27 high quality articles in areas of computer networking in the past three years including papers accepted by top conferences (e.g., SIGCOMM, SC, INFOCOM, ICNP, etc.) and top journals (e.g., TON, FGCS, etc.), and internet standard proposals accepted by IETF. Many works have been presented and demonstrated in some global events. SNLab will continue to make real impact in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The full proceedings can be downloaded here: &lt;a href=&#34;/files/tongji-yale-pub-2019.pdf&#34;&gt;[pdf]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Objective-Driven On-Demand Network Abstraction for Adaptive Applications</title>
      <link>/publication/gao-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/gao-2019/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update Algebra: Toward Continuous, Non-Blocking Composition of Network Updates in SDN</title>
      <link>/publication/ua-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/ua-2019/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Max-min Fair Allocation for Multi-source Transmission</title>
      <link>/publication/li-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/li-2019/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimizing in the Dark: Learning an Optimal Solution through a Simple Request Interface</title>
      <link>/publication/opt-box-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/opt-box-2019/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Precedence: Enabling Compact Program Layout By Table Dependency Resolution</title>
      <link>/publication/precedence-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/precedence-2019/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unicorn: Unified resource orchestration for multi-domain, geo-distributed data analytics</title>
      <link>/publication/unicorn-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/unicorn-2019/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fine-Grained, Multi-Domain Network Resource Abstraction as a Fundamental Primitive to Enable High-Performance, Collaborative Data Sciences</title>
      <link>/publication/re-sa-sc-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/re-sa-sc-19/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Congratulation: SNLab Published A Number of Top-Level Papers in Networking and System Areas in 2018</title>
      <link>/post/snlab-published-serveral-top-papers-in-networking-and-system-areas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 22:15:28 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/snlab-published-serveral-top-papers-in-networking-and-system-areas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In year 2018, the SNLab (Systems Networking Lab) at Tongji-Yale Center of
Advanced Networks and Networked Systems (TYCAN) led by Professor Y. Richard Yang
has published a number of top-level papers, including four CCF A papers accepted
by ACM SIGCOMM, IEEE INFOCOM (the top conferences in computer networking) and
SuperComputing (the top conference in computer systems) individually. The paper
&amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/prophet-infocom18&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Prophet: Fast Accurate Model-based Throughput Prediction forReactive Flow in
DC Networks&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;” is accepted by IEEE INFOCOM 2018.
This paper is completed by the Ph.D. student Jingxuan Zhang and collaborators
from Tsinghua University and Yale University. The paper “&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/capacity-theorem-infocom18&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Toward the First SDN
Programming Capacity Theorem on Realizing High-Level Programs on Low-Level
Datapaths&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;” is also received by IEEE
INFOCOM 2018. It is completed by the Ph.D. student Xin Wang during his visiting
student period at Yale University with others from Yale University. The paper
“&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/trident-sigcomm18&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Trident: Towards a Unified SDN Programming Framework with Automatic
Updates&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;” is accepted by ACM SIGCOMM 2018. The
paper “*Fine-Grained, Multi-Domain Network Resource Abstraction as a Fundamental
Primitive to Enable High-Performance, Collaborative Data Sciences*” is accepted
by SuperComputing 2018. The first author of this paper is Qiao Xiang, a
post-doctoral fellow of TYCAN; meanwhile, Xin Wang, Jingxuan Zhang and Yang Liu
are co-authors. Also, Qiao Xiang’s another paper “*OpenSDC: A Novel, Generic
Datapath for Software Defined Coalitions*” is accepted by IEEE MILCOM 2018, the
top conference in the military field. In addition, the paper “&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/ddp-icdcs18&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;DDP: Distributed
Network Updates in SDN&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;” is accepted by IEEE
ICDCS 2018. The first author of this paper is Geng Li, a post-doctoral fellow of
TYCAN. Yichen Qian, a Ph.D student at Tongji University, is one of the
co-authors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ACM SIGCOMM and IEEE INFOCOM are top conferences in computer networking, of
which SIGCOMM is the flagship conference in this field. The quality requirements
of the papers accepted by these two conferences are extremely strict. Many
significant papers in computer networking are published at these two
conferences. The SuperComputing (SC) conference, also known as International
Conference for High Performance Computing, Networking, Storage and Analysis, is
regarded as one of the world’s top academic conferences in the field of high
performance computing. The annually global TOP500 supercompuer list is released
through the SC, and the major manufactures and universities related to
super-calculation will be exhibited at the conference to show their latest
products and research results, so the SC conference has always been a great
event in the high-performance computing field. ICDCS is the top conference in
the field of distributed computing; and MILCOM is the flagship conference in the
military communications field.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 12:40:43 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;通知&#34;&gt;通知&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;同济-耶鲁联合网络实验室SNLab（坐标：&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.openstreetmap.org/way/266205932&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;电信学院219&lt;/a&gt;）正在招收研究生！&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;实验室由杨阳（&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.cs.yale.edu/homes/yry/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Y. Richard Yang&lt;/a&gt;）教授领导，主要从事下一代互联网架构及网络相关系统的研究。实验室自2015年创办以来，已在 IWQOS、ICDCS、DSC、INFOCOM、SIGCOMM 等计算机网络领域顶级会议上发表过多篇论文，并成功在开源网络操作系统 OpenDaylight 峰会和超级计算大会 SuperComputing 上进行过成果展示，以及 IETF 网络标准会议上主导多篇协议草案。实验室已培养多位成员赴 Yale、USC、NYU 等美国高校深造，或进入 Google、Facebook、华为等知名IT企业工作。在这里，你将有机会与来自 Caltech、ESNet、IBM、UCL 等国际组织的顶尖学者共同探讨学术问题，或与来自华为、腾讯等 IT 大厂的网络专家们探索工程实践的难题。我们期待更多有实力并对计算机网络与系统研究感兴趣的同学加入我们的团队！&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;主要面向对象&lt;/strong&gt;：数学、计算机及软件专业即将升入大四的本科生&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;实验室对招生无具体要求。只要你认为自己实力够强，并对计算机网络与系统研究感兴趣，均可投递简历至 &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:snlab.org@gmail.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;snlab.org@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;。我们期待你的加入！&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;以下为杨阳教授中文简历：&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/img/people/yry/yry_avatar1.png&#34; alt=&#34;Y. Richard Yang&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;杨阳，现任美国耶鲁大学终身正教授（Tenure）,国家特聘（千人）教授（同济），Tsinghua EMC Chaired Professor Group, Director of Undergraduate Studies (Yale), Director of Tongji-Yale Advanced Systems Center。在计算机互联网络领域中是迄今为止唯一在美国长春藤高校联盟中获得终身正教席的华人教授。谷歌学者(Google Scholar)收集论文总引用超24,000次，单篇论文最高引用次数为1567次，h-index达59。在国际互联网络领域最具影响力的顶级会议ACM SIGCOMM上，从2001年至今发表论文13篇，其中4篇获SIGCOMM最优论文提名，始终位于世界学者前列。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;杨阳教授的学术研究始于清华大学计算机系。他以新生入学数学选拔考试第一名入选清华因才施教生序列，以优异成绩作为优秀毕业生毕业，1993年被免试推荐攻读博士学位。 1996年获全额奖学金资助在全美计算机学科排名前十的德州大学奥斯丁分校（The University of Texas at Austin ）攻读博士学位并于2001年获计算机科学博士学位。自2001年起至今，在耶鲁大学计算机系任教，曾荣获2003年美国国家自然科学基金会杰出青年教授奖（NSF Career Award）， 2005年破格晋升为耶鲁计算机系副教授，以及电子工程系副教授，2009年获耶鲁终身教授（Tenure）席位，2013年四月以耶鲁计算机系全系全票通过正教授评审。2010年被清华大学兼聘为海外讲席教授组（EMC Chaired Professor Group）成员。2013年免面试入选国家千人计划专家。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;杨阳教授的研究领域跨越下一代互联网体系结构、软件定义网络、网络流量优化、互联网内容分发和云计算等多个重要领域，解决了多个互联网络所面临的基本理论挑战。杨阳教授坚持理论研究，国际标准，与网络应用相结合的学术风格。他是国际计算机网络领域中当前唯一一个既能够在顶级学术会议ACM SIGCOMM长期发表学术论文，同时又能在国际互联网标准组织(IETF)担当协议制定的学者。他所首创的P4P概念在国际互联网标准ALTO中得到采用，所提出的多个算法为多个全球最大的互联网设备与软件商（例如思科，华为，谷歌），互联网运行商（例如美国最大的Verizon，Comcast,欧洲最大的Telefonica,中国电信）采用或测试。当他受邀作为微软兼职研究员期间，他也参与了微软下一代操作系统Windows 8、 微软云计算Microsoft Azure等核心产品的设计和关键技术研发。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;具体在下一代互联网体系结构研究上，他领导、设计和实现的P4P架构提出了全新的网络与应用接口的概念，弥补了现有互联网架构应用与网络无有效沟通的基本缺陷，对下一代互联网体系结构产生了深远影响。P4P使用优化理论的对偶解合(Primal-Dual Decomposition)做为理论基础，提出了我的互联网（My-Internet)，PID等全新网络拓扑概念来设计新的互联网网络与应用接口。其理论结果发表于计算机网络领域最具影响力的会议ACM SIGCOMM 2008. P4P设计为福布斯、商业周刊、华盛顿邮报、英国经济人、卫报等权威媒体报道，并被美国联邦通讯委员会（FCC）引用。P4P在全球最大的六个运行商(AT&amp;amp;T, Bell Canada, Comcast, ChinaTelecom, Telefonica, Verizon)中得到成功测试和部署。基于P4P的ALTO互联网国际标准协议得到思科，谷歌等强力支持， 并被Google, Cisco, Juniper, Alcatel-Lucent， Telefonica, 中国电信等著名公司实现。扩充为QoSaaS架构，P4P理念也为微软的Lync所使用。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;在软件定义网络方向上，他所领导的Maple SDN编程语言获ACM SIGCOMM 2013最优论文提名，Trident理论结果发表于计算机网络国际顶级会议ACM SIGCOMM 2018. 其成果入选Open Network Summit最佳技术（Top 5 Technologies），2014 Google 研究奖（2014 Google Faculty Research Award），最大软件定义网络操作系统OpenDaylight领先技术，美国国家自然基金（NSF）部署奖（2014 NSF CC＊IIE Award），以及美国陆军与英国ITA项目十年支持（2017-2026）。&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;在网络流量优化领域上，杨阳教授研发的TORTE系统取得多个世界首创的理论突破，并在实际产品中得到应用。TORTE首创COPE (Common-Case Optimization with Penalty Optimization)原则，解决了网络面临的难以兼顾流量优化与可靠性的基本矛盾。COPE采用对偶理论来消除无限个约束变量。其理论结果发表于计算机网络领域最具影响力的会议ACM SIGCOMM 2006， 其实际算法被美国最大的网络运营商AT&amp;amp;T和世界最大的搜索公司Google采用。TORTE提出了首创的多址优化算法（Multihoming Optimization），成功解决了基础费用与质量优化之间的矛盾。TORTE的多址优化算法利用实际的互联网付费模型(p-percentile)来设计巧妙的优化原则，从而得到高效的算法。其理论结果发表在计算机网络领域最具影响力的会议ACM SIGCOMM 2004，实际算法被众多网络核心产品采用，如被思科（Cisco）IER所采用。TORTE首次提出了R3(Resilient Routing Reconfiguration)的新理念。 R3是第一个融入了流量工程策略的路由系统，可有效解决拓扑失败、流量抖动以及服务质量难以保障的难题。R3理论结果发表于计算机网络国际顶级会议ACM SIGCOMM 2010.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;在互联网内容分发与流媒体方面，杨阳教授领导的团队与中国最大的P2P视频门户PPLive合作，提出新颖的ShadowStream技术，解决了大规模流媒体服务难以测试的挑战. ShadowStream巧妙地利用已有的实际系统（Production System），让测试与实际系统并行，利用计算机求解与验证的基本非对称性(例如NP-Hard)来结合测试与实际系统。在互联网内容分发网络方面，他提出新颖的CMO(Content Multihoming Optimization)技术，领导解决了内容分发网络中如何有效降低成本与优化服务质量的基本难题。相关成果均发表在ACM SIGCOMM 2012。&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SFP: Toward Interdomain Routing for SDN Networks (Poster)</title>
      <link>/publication/sfp-poster-sigcomm18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 11:33:03 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/sfp-poster-sigcomm18/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fine-Grained, Multi-Domain Network Resource Abstraction as a Fundamental Primitive to Enable High-Performance, Collaborative Data Sciences (Poster)</title>
      <link>/publication/resa-poster-sigcomm18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 11:32:10 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/resa-poster-sigcomm18/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trident: toward a unified SDN programming framework with automatic updates</title>
      <link>/publication/trident-sigcomm18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 11:24:31 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/trident-sigcomm18/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DDP: Distributed Network Updates in SDN</title>
      <link>/publication/ddp-icdcs18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Aug 2018 11:18:41 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/ddp-icdcs18/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JMS: Joint Bandwidth Allocation and Flow Assignment for Transfers with Multiple Sources</title>
      <link>/publication/jms-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/jms-2018/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toward the First SDN Programming Capacity Theorem on Realizing High-Level Programs on Low-Level Datapaths</title>
      <link>/publication/capacity-theorem-infocom18/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 01:38:49 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/capacity-theorem-infocom18/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prophet: Fast Accurate Model-based Throughput Prediction for Reactive Flow in DC Networks</title>
      <link>/publication/prophet-infocom18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2018 01:38:37 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/prophet-infocom18/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game-Theoretic User Association in Ultra-dense Networks with Device-to-Device Relays</title>
      <link>/publication/li-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/li-2017/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NOVA: Towards on-demand equivalent network view abstraction for network optimization</title>
      <link>/publication/nova-iwqos17/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 11:09:34 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/nova-iwqos17/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ORSAP: Abstracting routing state on demand (Poster)</title>
      <link>/publication/orsap-poster-icnp16/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Nov 2016 11:01:47 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/orsap-poster-icnp16/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAST: A Simple Programming Abstraction for Complex State-Dependent SDN Programming (Poster)</title>
      <link>/publication/fast-poster-sigcomm16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 10:52:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/fast-poster-sigcomm16/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magellan: Generating Multi-Table Datapath from Datapath Oblivious Algorithmic SDN Policies (Poster)</title>
      <link>/publication/magellan-poster-sigcomm16/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 10:22:32 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/magellan-poster-sigcomm16/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Auc2Reserve: A Differentially Private Auction for Electric Vehicle Fast Charging Reservation (Invited Paper)</title>
      <link>/publication/auc-2-reserve-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/publication/auc-2-reserve-2016/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Richard Yang: SDN programming automation: abstraction, tools, and implementations</title>
      <link>/talk/sdn-programming-automation-abstraction-tools-and-applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2016 00:51:33 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/talk/sdn-programming-automation-abstraction-tools-and-applications/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SNLab Members attended the NSF Workshop on Algorithms for Software-Defined Networking</title>
      <link>/post/snlab-members-attended-the-nsf-workshop-on-algorithms/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 01:02:18 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/snlab-members-attended-the-nsf-workshop-on-algorithms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SNLab members (Hu Ning, Du Haizhou, Xiang Qiao, Pen Dan) recently attended the NSF Algorithms in the Field (AiTF) Workshop on Algorithms for Software-Defined Networking in June 2-3, 2016. This workshop is sponsored by the Algorithms in the Field (AiTF) program of the National Science Foundation and the DIMACS(Center for Discrete Mathematics &amp;amp; Theroetical Computer Science Technology Center). Including UC Berkeley, Stanford, Carnegie Mellon University, Princeton University, MIT, Google, Microsoft attended the workshop, and discuss together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main goal of this workshop is to bring together researchers working at the intersection of the theory and practice of networking, with a special focus on the applicability of these ideas to SDN, in the hope of jumpstarting collaborations between theoreticians and networking researchers in this area. This provide not only an opportunity for the networking community to get new ideas and approaches, but will also provide a tremendous opportunity for the theoretical community, both as a source of new algorithmic problems and as a way to have a direct impact. This is to some extent in contrast to the traditional networking paradigm, where the algorithmic problems often do not have a path to deployment as they are constrained by existing protocols.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/img/2016-06-14-snlab-members-attended-the-nsf-workshop-on-algorithms.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;NSF Workshop&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Xiang Qiao, represented the SNLab made a speech about Magellan: Toward Automatic Multi-Table SDN Programming. He systematic tell that Multi-table pipelining has emerged as a key technique for the next-generation SDN data path. Programming such a data path model, however, can be challenging. In this talk, he also discusses several algorithmic challenges in programming multi-table pipelines. This talk attracted both academic and industrial researchers. They gave some good suggestion and comments to us. And most of them highly agree with our research.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As this workshop, we discussed with the workshop attendees on the most important algorithmic problems involving SDN. This serves as a central point of reference for future work in algorithms for SDN, and hopefully spur further research in the way that lists of open problems have led to further research in other parts of algorithms.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARO Workshop on Software Defined Networking for Army Applications</title>
      <link>/post/aro-workshop-on-software-defined-networking-for-army-applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/aro-workshop-on-software-defined-networking-for-army-applications/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SNLab organized the workshop in May 5-6$^{th}$, 2016. This workshop bring together experts from software-defined networking, wireless/hybrid networks, tactical networks, high-performance computing and related disciplines to investigate both the benefits and the issues when applying SDN to army applications. The emergence of SDN, whose key features include separation between the data-plane and the control-plane of networks, and logically centralized network control, has potential to completely reshape the field of computer networking. Going beyond conceptual models, the existing deployment of SDN in major data centers (e.g., Google and Microsoft data centers) has demonstrated the substantial gain and flexibility of SDN. However, the existing initiatives of SDN focus mostly on non-tactical data center networks, service provider networks, and enterprise networks. Given the substantial potential of SDN, it is imperative that we develop a better understanding of both the impacts and the potential issues of applying SDN to Army Applications, primarily for multi-hop wireless/hybrid networks, but also for high performance computing in the army context.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We invited some famous professors and scientists to discuss some SDN challenge problem, including Yale, UCLA, Imperial College, University of Pennsylvania, Caltech, Carnegie Mellon University, Princeton University, MIT, DARPA, IBM, Uber etc. famous university and company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Y. Richard Yang as a chair , made a key note speech. And he introduced some recently research. A key benefit of SDN is logically centralized control. There is a large body of existing work of SDN control path, but they are mostly in the context of wired networks such as data center networks and wide-area networks (WAN). By control path, we mean the complete spectrum from controller placement, controller fault tolerance, controller programming, and controller-forwarding elements integration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This workshop reviewed key related work and warmly discussed issues with potential outcomes. The workshop successful hold and all of attendees are very satisfied with the outcome of the workshop.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Demonstration of ALTO SPEC on 2016 Internet2 Global Summit</title>
      <link>/post/demonstration-of-alto-spce-on-2016-internet2-global-summit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/demonstration-of-alto-spce-on-2016-internet2-global-summit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;2016 Internet2 Global Summit&lt;/em&gt; was successfully held in Chicago, Illinois on May 15 to May 18.The Internet2 Global Summit is a leading forum to support and drive the advancement of research and education, spur next-generation innovation and accelerate global discovery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SNlab cooperated with CERN from Caltech on the discussion and demonstration of latest achievements among this summit. Core members including Jensen Zhang, Mingming Chen, Qiao Xiang, Kai Gao, May Wang and Shawn Lin attended the summit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Achievements on development of ALTO SPCE was presented and received great acclaim from attendees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/static/img/2016-05-31-demonstration-of-alto-spce-on-2016-internet2-global-summit-1.png&#34; alt=&#34;ALTO SPCE Demo&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SNlab&amp;rsquo;s major work is based on the SDN controller OpenDaylight. This demonstration is bulit on the environment provided by Caltech, with several Pica8 and SDN switches(from Dell) and work with standard protocol OpenFlow to connect OpenDaylight. The convertion from virtual environment to the real is a great breakthrough .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/static/img/2016-05-31-demonstration-of-alto-spce-on-2016-internet2-global-summit-2.png&#34; alt=&#34;CMS Experiment&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SNlab and Caltech will keep working  together on the great issues of SDN.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Summit of SNLab Held</title>
      <link>/post/spring-summit-of-snlab-held/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/spring-summit-of-snlab-held/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Spring Summit of SNlab is held on March 21 to March 23 in College of Computer Science, Tongji University.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Summit invited researchers from Qinghua, Yale, University of Science and Technology, Shanghai Jiao Tong University, Nanjing University of Posts and telecommunications and Chinese Academy of Sciences to engage in the summit.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
