<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dawn Chan | SNLab - Systems Networking Lab</title>
    <link>/authors/dawn-chan/</link>
      <atom:link href="/authors/dawn-chan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Dawn Chan</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 22:15:28 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/img/icon-192.png</url>
      <title>Dawn Chan</title>
      <link>/authors/dawn-chan/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Congratulation: SNLab Published A Number of Top-Level Papers in Networking and System Areas in 2018</title>
      <link>/post/snlab-published-serveral-top-papers-in-networking-and-system-areas/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 22:15:28 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/snlab-published-serveral-top-papers-in-networking-and-system-areas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In year 2018, the SNLab (Systems Networking Lab) at Tongji-Yale Center of
Advanced Networks and Networked Systems (TYCAN) led by Professor Y. Richard Yang
has published a number of top-level papers, including four CCF A papers accepted
by ACM SIGCOMM, IEEE INFOCOM (the top conferences in computer networking) and
SuperComputing (the top conference in computer systems) individually. The paper
&amp;ldquo;&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/prophet-infocom18&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Prophet: Fast Accurate Model-based Throughput Prediction forReactive Flow in
DC Networks&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;” is accepted by IEEE INFOCOM 2018.
This paper is completed by the Ph.D. student Jingxuan Zhang and collaborators
from Tsinghua University and Yale University. The paper “&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/capacity-theorem-infocom18&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Toward the First SDN
Programming Capacity Theorem on Realizing High-Level Programs on Low-Level
Datapaths&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;” is also received by IEEE
INFOCOM 2018. It is completed by the Ph.D. student Xin Wang during his visiting
student period at Yale University with others from Yale University. The paper
“&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/trident-sigcomm18&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Trident: Towards a Unified SDN Programming Framework with Automatic
Updates&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;” is accepted by ACM SIGCOMM 2018. The
paper “*Fine-Grained, Multi-Domain Network Resource Abstraction as a Fundamental
Primitive to Enable High-Performance, Collaborative Data Sciences*” is accepted
by SuperComputing 2018. The first author of this paper is Qiao Xiang, a
post-doctoral fellow of TYCAN; meanwhile, Xin Wang, Jingxuan Zhang and Yang Liu
are co-authors. Also, Qiao Xiang’s another paper “*OpenSDC: A Novel, Generic
Datapath for Software Defined Coalitions*” is accepted by IEEE MILCOM 2018, the
top conference in the military field. In addition, the paper “&lt;a href=&#34;/publication/ddp-icdcs18&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;DDP: Distributed
Network Updates in SDN&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;” is accepted by IEEE
ICDCS 2018. The first author of this paper is Geng Li, a post-doctoral fellow of
TYCAN. Yichen Qian, a Ph.D student at Tongji University, is one of the
co-authors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ACM SIGCOMM and IEEE INFOCOM are top conferences in computer networking, of
which SIGCOMM is the flagship conference in this field. The quality requirements
of the papers accepted by these two conferences are extremely strict. Many
significant papers in computer networking are published at these two
conferences. The SuperComputing (SC) conference, also known as International
Conference for High Performance Computing, Networking, Storage and Analysis, is
regarded as one of the world’s top academic conferences in the field of high
performance computing. The annually global TOP500 supercompuer list is released
through the SC, and the major manufactures and universities related to
super-calculation will be exhibited at the conference to show their latest
products and research results, so the SC conference has always been a great
event in the high-performance computing field. ICDCS is the top conference in
the field of distributed computing; and MILCOM is the flagship conference in the
military communications field.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
